it's just some title eating we're moving
very much looking to rent a home this
has been really good for us empty I'm
sure at all this there's no more no more
secrets
yeah we can't forget that poster yep and
a Calvi side whiteboard no secrets
wait is the basement empty
yeah it's great yeah oh yeah okay right
yeah oh my god yeah oh my god Wow
nope you guys realize the monstrosity of
this but this is nothing this is this is
top secret stuff yeah this is really
important don't tell them yeah okay but
this is the top yep and it's front
that's the prom yeah he did we pierce
holes in there for the don't worry about
that have you packed yeah that's fine
all right folks we just wanna see ya ray
any questions I don't really know I
haven't been like
lately gone assessment of what I walk
for me inside of them it's just
emotional you think this is the same
link this the 'saturday cell one that we
did
no not little olena yeah I think it is
no we don't have any lives for that my
folks were out we wanted to take a back
piece way it's been so long